The full form of OPD is
in medical terms and patient department
so that if you are cancelling the doctor,
who is the first point of contact,
that is the generation, take property consultancy,
you understand what has happened to your health
and what statement should be taken, it is
not necessary that you have to be hospitalized for everything,
that too can be
treated in treatment, after consultation from the office, get the
medicine also tested, you will be fine,
OPD treatment is not covered in many policies,
what happens, it is minimal to negligible,
then
you have this question that which
plants are there, if you want to take only the epicenter of
class, which
plant is available for them, then today I did research from those two plants
and am making a video for you,
two plants are Max Bupa
Lemon * Triphala and Isolation Ward
Help A Lip Length, so I will talk about these two,
before starting the video
I would like to tell you, for those who have used
my name is Cooling and Chiku, I am
Sahitya Narhari, I make videos for you,
soda my real  Life insurance point of view
makes youth quite happy because
this is our company's side creating
welfare and from the last two months we are
also bringing team videos for every World Cup
so you must be thinking that you
could have taken a policy from war to those
who
can stay
and
subscribe
and there is a
policy type in both clans Aftab
Individual Family Floater both options you
can always take and if we talk about
lemon round plant minimum review
is available flight maximum is
25 lakh AC number in health tips minimum
Someshwar double fault maximum is if you are
looking at it then you can write in Hindi
under-25 box is the patient like this then you
can see romance we will talk about room
rent eligibility I will fulfill active but if it is a phone
launch policy then one per cent of sum
assured your room rent cutting is from 5 lakh
to toilet this is the policy so single
private AC room mine take it in Magh Mela
audience will talk about cutting eye serum
Similar in the room if the
policy is below Chawla lemon positive then 2% you all
Vishal and if you are above lakh then there is
no typing is a not help there is no
topic in the playlist on this room
also so if we talk about hospitalization then
Nibha Quarter Pimpri is unwanted
specialization power from this there is number for health
and it is a hurt prevent actress
award see text message
in both the films cover up to some assured AYUSH
hospitalization AYUSH is Ayurvedic
Unani Siddha Homeopathy hospitalization
news both are not balance but all
wards if we talk about no claim bonus then there is
no contact of no claim bonus in loss on lemon there is a WhatsApp we will
understand that but in this low might help the no
claim bonus is minimum nine percent every
year maximum will be up to 50% it is called
additional commissioner also
in their language SI is a leader it is inbuilt in it
that if your exams i.e. ginger in any year
so meat is below software then
this will not be sides so the additional  If you have got a commissioner then it will
not be reduced by 50%
and a reminder for you ad 2002, if we talk about
agency road ambulance in this twelfth plan then
lemon was in quarter
only, hospitalization is at ₹1 itself but he said
scent of mixture on your hair,
if your time is less in terms of health then
your Arora Munshi limit becomes,
if you can live above Rs.10000 then
road ambulance will be reversed, but if we
talk about hospitalization emergency ambulance then there is
no comment in Nibha item, the longest
hole is emergency rest violation, now it is
included shot and this time is up to you special
description box MS Word, so this will not be in the account,
Malviya ji, if you have used the emergency ambulance now then it will
not be in front of me, this news will always be on the
next home health care services, that means
if you want to get treatment at home and do
not want to go to the hospital, then that is also our account,
very policy commissioner hospitalization
means treatment at home, it is not in the condition
that you can go to the hospital and the other is
not sitting in the hospital, then both
In the condition, the hospitalization rate increases
and both the cities including Kavad pilgrims will
talk in balance. The distance benefit of mutual benefit is
that if your base
is always over then it becomes rear, that is
equal to Ramesh Bhatt again, the company gives
you real benefit, there is
no extra help for it, so keeping this in mind,
100% is available for different purposes only,
unlimited number of sciences are available in my IS A BOTTLE playlist,
you can use it only for different tailors,
living organ transplant
is covered in both, you will get it on Saturday, from
time to time, in such moments, there are five
lines about LIC policy in the bag, so now you
understand that the living donor slide which will be decorated, if
my stuffing is above one lakh
then maximum of 10 lakh will be given for organ
donor transplant, now let's talk about
OPD benefit, we had started
this line on the basis of OPD benefits, we get it, so let's
talk in OPD  First we will
talk about lemon per quarter, so here on the
consultation is on the mass that as
you take the concentration, it is
designed according to that consultation, how many consultations
you can take and how much consultation you will get, so there are
different
combinations here, for example, if you have a
duplex deprived youth, then the tension
limit is three consultations maximum in flight,
in Chawla Public Policy you can take fault time and 7.5 more consultations in it,
maximum from tablet to
twelfth class policy
you can take six consultations or again upwards
then you can launch the phone there, you can
take subscription
in that policy, you can take one more
subscription here of concentration which
they have limited,
so you
mean maximum if you deposit
above 10 lakhs then subscription is 269 and
if you make a phone call then there is consultation here, then
education content 250,
this festival of Mitthu is reimbursement in both ways  If you
want to tighten it, then you
can note the first chapter of lemon. You can book your
appointment with the doctor where their
tube is. If you want to see your doctor, then
this is the limit. I have
told you that you will get it. You
can apply for it and it gets
applied through the application. Earlier, you had to
submit that line to claim for every
time. Now it is easy. Now you
can apply through the application and try it. We will
talk about it. The number six oil,
there is a limit of Rs.
50 in your policy, which you can click on in a year.
You can change 10 polythene of tempered glass
and shift your debit Tubelight
in LIC policy. There is
no combination of material definition here,
that this is the combination. That is, this much consultation is
according to the time of examination
and if your leave time is left, then
maximum Rs. 20,000 can be opened for the question.
Now let's come.  Motivated
to benefit is what happened with the generation,
this benefit is
not really covered in the romantic playlist, if you take it in Delhi then there is a
word of maternity benefit
in the policy of 5 lakhs, in normal, supreme
power in the morning, there is also a design on reaching Amazon Prince,
2015 video 1000, similarly if you take today's
policy then you will get 350 in normal,
in normal delivery you
could get more than 130
mix, for confidence loss you can
subscribe to my channel, do
not forget to get
your airplane or
diagnostic test done, it has limited
side, so you will not get policy matter
of pilot, if it is of thousand
rupees for adult member, if it is
between 1.5 and back then if it is run on the force adult number
then ₹500 pilot member
is in, you can click on this, you can get any
test done and get it reimbursed, there is a
program in it, behavioral  You
can subscribe by clicking on continue here, so
this is for you to
subscribe to, if you are focusing on
medical, then you are looking at it, then you
can tell it with lemon and unlimited union from here and you can
take tension in a different way, we will talk about model sequence, there are
some limits in modern treatment, which
I will
tell you, so
first
enter separately, then you have to
subscribe, like,
share and subscribe us for this, so
you
can subscribe if you want to
use it
and you will use it, then every tempered
glass
is friends, I have done video coach,
you can sign up for personal life help course,
you will get that additional
help, then it will focus on your different
seriousness, it will focus on your balance,
personal life 1215 city police station service
admission, you will get some points which will give you
20% on renewal premium, you can
click on horoscope, next is personal
accidental cover, you can use it, you will see
good points in it, total disability
pension possibility, this is the file, now you will come
Scheduled Tribes
is still available in Delhi. First which Vasant benefit
if you are hospitalized above Lucknow, if you are
not near you then this Bansal friend will give you
more than 150 rupees that these protractors
are non-tribal items, if you pay the
premium of these protractors then
their goods should protect them in this
world will be increased every year as per her
complexion if you use then
always follow the album play list hisab
mixture up knock advanced it job
Monsanto inverter policy has super no
claim bonus, then on that you get
additional 50% above no claim bonus and the maximum
goes up to 200%, so you can
see the no claim bonus additional premium on that, next
critically injured critical
illness you can get cover of 5 lakh, 7 lakh or
10 lakh policy, if you have a
policy of more than 3 lakh from time to time then 50%
is always your eligibility, next is personal
accidental news also appoint  You can do that the
limit is two including questions so that they can change the
situations and in every policy like there are some
activations that serial event is
not intense you can change it whenever we will
talk in the initial meeting it is for
30 days first you cannot plan hospitalization for some time there are
specific tuitions which are some things
which people will stay in called massacre there will be
no interruption for 2 years both the policies
in this there is a problem of waiting period of lion more than before which will
not happen till then bye-bye
thank you that at the end how much is the premium
I have taken here
I have put 49 trailers and this is the
cream that you are watching then you
get 3363 in a year if
I subscribe
and if we
talk about six means scooty then it is
2030 of this which you
can subscribe for a total of 10 years okay if you have
not subscribed to the channel yet then
subscribe and increase it will tell you how it is done in this video so
sometime help me  I
know what you want to see, so it would have been
easy to mail you on what to make the next video on,
okay, see you again, like, share and
take care, bye-bye, kar do
[music]
kar do
ki a
[music] hua